kevro.co.za 2016-04-01

# Privacy Policy | Kevro

Overview  
This web site is owned and operated by Kevro Trading (Pty) Ltd t/a Kevro (“Kevro”), a company registered in the Republic of South Africa under company registration number 2011/123904/07, which has its registered office at 25 Nguni Drive, Longmeadow, Business Estate West, Modderfontein, Johannesburg, 1609.

Kevro has a firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following statement explains our policy in regard to the use of any personal information you may give us as you use any part of www.kevro.co.za. We can be reached via e-mail at customercare@kevro.co.za.

Information Collection and Use  
We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our web site, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and address). 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify consumers about updates to our web site, and used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes. We do not sell or share your personal information to others or any affiliates. We send promotional information in compliance with the Electronic Communications and Transactions Act, 2002. Our computer system protects personal information using advanced firewall technology.

With respect to Ad Servers, we do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

Site Security and Cookies  
With respect to security, we have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. For credit card transactions, Kevro adds security by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. This means that the credit card information you send is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our side, preventing others from accessing your private information in between.

Most non-personal information is collected via cookies. Kevro may use cookies to enhance the user experience and personalize content. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your hard drive and identifies you as a unique user. Cookies help the Company understand which areas of the website are most popular to help improve the user experience on future visits.

Personal Information  
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. Persons who supply us with their email address online may receive email marketing from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. 

Revisions to the Privacy Statement  
If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at customercare@kevro.co.za.
